<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="64">
    <author>EDGE Gaming</author>
    <translationby>Castiga</translationby>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title><!-- en=English de=German jp=Japanese pl=Polish cz=Czech fr=French es=Spanish ru=Russian it=Italian pt=Portuguese hu=Hungary nl=Netherlands cs=Chinese (Simplified) ct=Chinese (Traditional) br=Brazilian-Portuguese tr=Turkish ro=Romanian kr=Korean -->
        <en>Crater Bay</en>
        <de>Crater Bay</de>
        <fr>Crater Bay</fr>
        <es>Crater Bay</es>
        <ru>Кратер Бэй</ru>
        <pl>Zatoka Kraterowa</pl>
        <it>Crater Bay</it>
        <br>Crater Bay</br>
        <cs>火山口湾</cs>
        <ct>火山口灣</ct>
        <cz>Crater Bay</cz>
        <nl>Crater Bay</nl>
        <hu>Crater Bay</hu>
        <jp>クレーターベイ</jp>
        <kr>크레이터 베이</kr>
        <pt>Crater Bay</pt>
        <ro>Crater Bay</ro>
        <tr>Krater Körfezi</tr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Welcome to Crater Bay.

Crater Bay has emerged! a Huge Island Inspired by Nosy Be island (Antsiranana Province) off the North West coast of Madagascar with all FS19 features.
You will find a rundown farm on a Huge, Hilly & overgown Island, the area has been left behind by active farmers due to bad ferry connection.
Now its up to you to get the land back in functioning order.
You start off with a small farm and a field + Silo & Vehicles on New Farmer, work your way all alound this huge map to set the land back in perfact idyllic condition.
The map is Highly costumizeable with several large open areas & smaller areas made specificly for rebuilding, so you can Customize it just how you like it. this makes it ideal for multiplayer, but also great for Singleplayer as you will never run out of things to do.
We have added a ton of ground textures and Foliage you can paint in game for total freedom!
The Main farm is placed pretty centered on the island, only a little to the north, and you have all facilities spread around you, and all you need to get your farm back in business.
Can you make Crater Bay shine like it should? or will you find a ferry back to the mainland?

Climate of Crater Bay:
On the north-west coast, temperatures are high all year round, but being that it's directly exposed to the northwest monsoon, the rains are more abundant, so much so that they exceed 2,000 mm (80 in) in some areas.
In Nosy-Be, an island located a short distance from the coast of Ambanja, the decrease in temperatures from May to August is limited.
Not only the period from November to March is rainy, but it's also hot and muggy. We are in the austral summer, a season when the country is divided into two: in the north, the north-west monsoon prevails, bringing heavy rains along the north-west coast, where rainfall is around 400/500 mm (16/20 in) per month in January and February.

The sun in Nosy Be shines very often in the dry period, from May to October. On average, there are almost 3,000 sunshine hours per year.
In this part of the coast, the sea temperature is high throughout the year

Info:
The map is 4x size with loads of fields, and customizing opportunities.
The forester manager is also taken care of. The map Contains loads of Forest areas that offers enough trees for any Logger.
It Offers several Bio Gas Plants (BGA) for the silage farmer.
As a special feature, a green floor is built in to create store photos that can be painted using the Landscaping Tool. In the shop there is also a green wall (without collision), which can be placed to create a green box.

The terrain is surrounded by a Ocean. The only access is unfortunately via Ferry, and it doesnt seem to go to often. Fortunately, there is you as the supplier of idyllic Crater Bay. So, what are you waiting for? Have fun!

Features:
- greenbox by soil texture and placeable wall
- 33 fields ranking in between Small & Huge
- forest areas
- biogas plant
- Several outlets for all standard fruits
- 2x New Fruits (also made more channels in the fruits so it doesnt restict on maximum fruits)
- with or without Farm buildings and vehicles (depending on the level of difficulty)
- AI-pedestrian and -traffic
- Several water triggers, also Ocean all around.
- a lime silo
- an Immersive mission system, with tons & tons of different Missions. (including transport orders)
- livestock is not permanently installed

-The map fully supports "Seasons" and "Courseplay Six".

- Consider Getting the Seasons GEO: Crater Bay Mod
Seasons GEO: Crater Bay is a GEO mod for Seasons that simulates agriculture in Crater Bay, Nosy Be (Antsiranana Province) on the Northern Coast of Madagascar.
with realistic temperatures, wind & rainfall taken from wather statistics from this area.

Upcomming Updates 1.5.0.0:
- Adding "RICE" as a crop to the map. As this is Madagascar's Biggest Crop Export!

-If you find any bugs or got suggestions for improvment, please dont hesitate to contact us on our Github page at https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
or Contact EDGEPureGaming on facebook.]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Multi Verkaufsstation. Hier können Sie alles verkaufen, was Sie möchten, von der Ernte bis zu Saatgut und Dünger.
Die Verkaufspreise schwanken und erscheinen auf dem PDA / der Statistik.
Die Gebäude verfügen über eine automatische Beleuchtung.

Änderungsprotokoll 1.0.0.0:
- Erstveröffentlichung.

-Wenn Sie Fehler finden oder Verbesserungsvorschläge haben, zögern Sie bitte nicht, uns auf unserer Github-Seite unter https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
zu kontaktieren oder EDGEPureGaming auf Facebook zu kontaktieren.]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Poste de vente multiple. Ici, vous pouvez vendre ce que vous voulez, de la récolte aux semences et aux engrais.
Les prix de vente fluctueront et apparaîtront sur le PDA / Statistics.
Les bâtiments ont un éclairage automatique.

Changer le journal 1.0.0.0:
- Première version.

-Si vous trouvez des bugs ou avez des suggestions d'amélioration, n'hésitez pas à nous contacter sur notre page Github à https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
ou Contacter EDGEPureGaming sur facebook.]]></fr>
        <es><![CDATA[Estación De Venta Múltiple. Aquí puede vender lo que quiera, desde la cosecha hasta las semillas y los fertilizantes.
Los precios de venta fluctuarán y aparecerán en el PDA / Estadísticas.
Los edificios tienen iluminación automática.

Registro de cambios 1.0.0.0:
- Versión inicial.

-Si encuentra algún error u obtiene sugerencias de mejora, no dude en contactarnos en nuestra página de Github en https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
o póngase en contacto con EDGEPureGaming en Facebook.]]></es>
        <ru><![CDATA[Мультипродажная станция. Здесь вы можете продать все, что захотите, от сбора урожая до семян и удобрений.
Продажные цены будут колебаться и отображаться на КПК / Статистика.
Здания имеют автоматическое освещение.

Изменения 1.0.0.0:
- Первый выпуск.

-Если вы обнаружите какие-либо ошибки или получите предложения по улучшению, пожалуйста, не стесняйтесь связаться с нами на нашей странице Github по адресу https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
или связаться с EDGEPureGaming на Facebook.]]></ru>
        <pl><![CDATA[Stacja Sprzedaży. Tutaj możesz sprzedać wszystko, co chcesz, od zbiorów upraw po nasiona i nawozy.
Ceny sprzedaży będą się zmieniać i pojawiać na PDA / statystykach.
Budynki mają automatyczne oświetlenie.

Lista zmian 1.0.0.0:
- Pierwsze wydanie.

-Jeśli znajdziesz jakieś błędy lub masz sugestie dotyczące ulepszeń, nie wahaj się skontaktować z nami na naszej stronie Github pod adresem https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
lub Skontaktuj się z EDGEPureGaming na Facebooku.]]></pl>
        <it><![CDATA[Turbo Kipper è un ottimo rimorchio per tutti i tuoi lavori agricoli. Ha una capacità di 50.000 litri e viene fornito con un giunto di attacco posteriore se mai hai bisogno di fare un treno stradale,
mettici sopra un carrello e fai bene ad attaccare qualcos'altro dietro.
Viene fornito con tonnellate di possibilità di costumizzazione e molte configurazioni delle ruote, nonché vernice completamente personalizzabile! Ottieni quel colore di fattoria sul tuo rimorchio a!

Questo meraviglioso rimorchio avrà il potere di fare tutto ciò di cui hai bisogno nella tua fattoria, a patto che i tuoi macchinari abbiano il potere di tirarlo!

Buona agricoltura.

Di seguito troverai una descrizione dettagliata:

--Informazioni tecniche--
Turbo Kipper:
Prezzo: 65.000 €
Dimensioni: 3,5 x 11 metri.
Capacità: 50.000 litri.
Peso: 5900 kg
Potenza consigliata: 250 CV +
Giunti Attacher: gancio di traino posteriore.

-Supporta "Stagioni", "Courseplay Six" e "MaizePlus".

-Se trovi qualche bug o hai suggerimenti per l'improvvisazione, non esitare a contattarci sulla nostra pagina Github all'indirizzo https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
o Contatta EDGEPureGaming su Facebook.]]></it>
        <br><![CDATA[-Se você encontrar algum erro ou tiver sugestões de melhorias, não hesite em entrar em contato conosco em nossa página do Github em https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
ou Entre em contato com a EDGEPureGaming no facebook.]]></br>
        <cs><![CDATA[-如果您发现任何错误或有改进建议，请随时通过我们的Github页面与我们联系，网址为https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
或在Facebook上联系EDGEPureGaming。]]></cs>
        <ct><![CDATA[-如果您發現任何錯誤或需要改進的建議，請隨時通過我們的Github頁面與我們聯繫，網址為https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
或在Facebook上聯繫EDGEPureGaming。]]></ct>
        <cz><![CDATA[- Pokud najdete nějaké chyby nebo návrhy na zlepšení, neváhejte nás kontaktovat na naší stránce Github na adrese https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
nebo kontaktujte EDGEPureGaming na facebooku.]]></cz>
        <nl><![CDATA[-Als u bugs vindt of suggesties voor verbetering krijgt, aarzel dan niet om contact met ons op te nemen op onze Github-pagina op https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
of neem contact op met EDGEPureGaming op Facebook.]]></nl>
        <hu><![CDATA[-Als u bugs vindt of suggesties voor verbetering krijgt, aarzel dan niet om contact met ons op te nemen op onze Github-pagina op https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
of neem contact op met EDGEPureGaming op Facebook.]]></hu>
        <jp><![CDATA[-バグを見つけたり、改善のための提案を得た場合は、https：//github.com/FS19-Mods-By-EDGE/のGithubページでお気軽にお問い合わせください。
またはfacebookでEDGEPureGamingに連絡してください。]]></jp>
        <kr><![CDATA[-버그를 발견하거나 즉흥 개선을위한 제안이 있으면 Github 페이지 (https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/)로 문의하십시오.
또는 페이스 북에서 EDGEPureGaming에 문의하십시오.]]></kr>
        <pt><![CDATA[-Se você encontrar algum erro ou tiver sugestões de melhorias, não hesite em entrar em contato conosco em nossa página do Github em https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
ou Entre em contato com a EDGEPureGaming no facebook.]]></pt>
        <ro><![CDATA[-Dacă găsiți buguri sau aveți sugestii de îmbunătățire, nu ezitați să ne contactați pe pagina noastră Github la https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/
sau Contactați EDGEPureGaming pe facebook.]]></ro>
        <tr><![CDATA[-Herhangi bir hata bulursanız veya iyileştirme önerileriniz varsa, lütfen https://github.com/FS-Mods-By-EDGE/ adresindeki Github sayfamızdan bizimle iletişime geçmekten çekinmeyin.
veya Facebook'ta EDGEPureGaming ile iletişime geçin.]]></tr>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>Crater_Bay_icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc/modDesc_l10n"/>
    <maps>
        <map id="Crater Bay" className="Mission00" filename="$dataS/scripts/missions/mission00.lua" configfilename="craterBay/map.xml" defaultVehiclesXMLfilename="craterBay/vehicles.xml" defaultPlaceablesXMLfilename="craterBay/placeables.xml" defaultItemsXMLfilename="craterBay/items.xml">
            <title>
                <en>Crater Bay</en>
                <de>Crater Bay</de>
                <fr>Crater Bay</fr>
                <it>Crater Bay</it>
                <es>Crater Bay</es>
                <br>Crater Bay</br>
                <cs>Crater Bay</cs>
                <ct>Crater Bay</ct>
                <cz>Crater Bay</cz>
                <nl>Crater Bay</nl>
                <hu>Crater Bay</hu>
                <jp>エスタンシアラパチョ</jp>
                <kr>Crater Bay</kr>
                <pl>Crater Bay</pl>
                <pt>Crater Bay</pt>
                <ro>Crater Bay</ro>
                <ru>Crater Bay</ru>
                <tr>Crater Bay</tr>
            </title>
            <description>
                <en><![CDATA[Crater Bay has emerged! a Huge Island Inspired by Nosy Be island (Antsiranana Province) off the North West coast of Madagascar with all FS19 features.
You will find a rundown farm on a Huge, Hilly & overgown Island, the area has been left behind by active farmers due to bad ferry connection.
Now its up to you to get the land back in functioning order.]]></en>
                <de><![CDATA[Multi Verkaufsstation. Hier können Sie alles verkaufen, was Sie möchten, von der Ernte bis zu Saatgut und Dünger.
        Die Verkaufspreise schwanken und erscheinen auf dem PDA / der Statistik.
        Die Gebäude verfügen über eine automatische Beleuchtung.]]></de>
                <fr><![CDATA[Poste de vente multiple. Ici, vous pouvez vendre ce que vous voulez, de la récolte aux semences et aux engrais.
        Les prix de vente fluctueront et apparaîtront sur le PDA / Statistics.
        Les bâtiments ont un éclairage automatique.]]></fr>
                <es><![CDATA[Estación De Venta Múltiple. Aquí puede vender lo que quiera, desde la cosecha hasta las semillas y los fertilizantes.
        Los precios de venta fluctuarán y aparecerán en el PDA / Estadísticas.
        Los edificios tienen iluminación automática.]]></es>
                <ru><![CDATA[Мультипродажная станция. Здесь вы можете продать все, что захотите, от сбора урожая до семян и удобрений.
        Продажные цены будут колебаться и отображаться на КПК / Статистика.
        Здания имеют автоматическое освещение.]]></ru>
                <pl><![CDATA[Stacja Sprzedaży. Tutaj możesz sprzedać wszystko, co chcesz, od zbiorów upraw po nasiona i nawozy.
        Ceny sprzedaży będą się zmieniać i pojawiać na PDA / statystykach.
        Budynki mają automatyczne oświetlenie.]]></pl>
                <it>Benvenuto all’Crater Bay!</it>
                <es>¡Te damos la bienvenida a Crater Bay!</es>
                <br>Bem-vindo à Crater Bay!</br>
                <cs>欢迎来到紫檀大庄园！</cs>
                <ct>歡迎來到紫檀大莊園！</ct>
                <cz>Vítejte v Crater Bay!</cz>
                <nl>Welkom op de Crater Bay!</nl>
                <hu>Üdvözöl Crater Bay!</hu>
                <jp>エスタンシアラパチョにようこそ！</jp>
                <kr>Crater Bay에 오신 것을 환영합니다!</kr>
                <pt>Bem-vindo à Crater Bay!</pt>
                <ro>Bun venit la Crater Bay!</ro>
                <tr>Crater Bay'ya hoş geldin!</tr>
            </description>
            <iconFilename>Crater_Bay_preview.dds</iconFilename>
        </map>
    </maps>
    <!--<storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/vehicles/lizardWeight550/lizardWeight550.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/vehicles/DeutzAgroStar661/deutzAgroStar661.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/placeables/gasStation.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/placeables/Food_n_Fertilizer_Shop/FoodFertilizerShop.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/placeables/Multi_Selling_Station/data/MultiSellingStationDark.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="maps/data/placeables/StrawBarn_SellingSpot/data/StrawBarn_SellingSpot_White.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
    <filltypes>
        <fillType name="POPPY_FLOWER" title="POPPY_FLOWER"/>
        <fillType name="HEMP" title="HEMP"/>
        <fillType name="HEMP_PLANT" title="HEMP_PLANT"/>
        <fillType name="POPPY" title="POPPY"/>
    </filltypes>-->
    <brands>
        <brand name="EDGE" title="EDGE Industries" image="icons/EDGE_Brand_Logo.dds"/>
        <brand name="LIMAGRAIN" title="Limagrain" image="icons/Limagrain_Logo.dds"/>
    </brands>
    <credits><![CDATA[
## Contributors
- Castiga, EDGE Gaming
## Translations
- Castiga
## Designers
- Trojan horse, Castiga]]></credits>
</modDesc>
